TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
음, 그렇게... 그래서...
Well... that's... what happened...
그게 뭔 소리에요!
What do you mean by that?!
아니, 그게, 선생님도 말야, 이대로 괜찮지 않을까 싶었는데, 그렇게는 안 된다는 거 같다는
Well, that is, I thought that it is fine as just it is now, but they say it is not allowed,
의견이 이렇게 나오고 이렇게 안 나오고 그렇게 여기서 다시 생각하는 게 좋겠다 싶어서...
while some say so, so some agree and some don't, and I thought you should make a decision.
그러니까 신문부하고 방송부하고 합병하라는 거에요?!
So are you asking us to merge Newspaper Club and Broadcasting Club?!
이건 사이좋게... 하는 건 대부분 비슷하고 말야...
You should get along with him... both clubs do similar things, too...
학교도 이건 사치는 안 된다... 하는 것 같고 말이야.
It seems that the school is considering this as extravagant, also...
그런 것 같다니...
It seems so...?
전 괜찮아요. 혼자라면 귀찮아 보이고요.
I'm fine with that. Doing all that by oneself looks bothersome, too.
정말이냐, 마스이즈미!
Is that true, Masuizumi?
흥, 취재 방법 알고 싶으면 알려줄게.
Hmph. If you want to learn about how to cover a news, I'll teach you.
그 쪽이 내 쪽으로 흡수되는 거잖아.
Your one is gonna be merged with mine, you know.
왜 신문부가 방송부 따위에! 그 쪽이 내 쪽에 올 거야!
Why would Broadcasting Club take Newspaper Club in?! Your one will be merged to mine!
부원 혼자인 주제에!
You're the only member of your club!
너야말로!
You too!
똑바로 된 도구도 없잖아.
You don't even have proper tools.
헤, 비디오나 카메라가 멋대로 취재해 주냐?
Oh, are you saying that your camcorder makes a news for you?
그새 변명이나 바꾸고 말야. 꼴불견이네.
And you already changed your excuses? How unsightly.
자랑할 건 도구나 그 잘난 입밖에 없냐?
Are your tools and your big mouth everything you've got to boast?
자, 자, 그만, 그만.
Now, now, yeah, get along with it.
뭐랄지, 이건 둘이서 잘 이야기해서 해결하는 게 제일일 거라 선생님은 생각해.
Well, I think it is best for you two to talk to solve this problem together.
이거 나이스 아이디어.
Isn't it a nice idea?
흥.
Hmph.
이야기할 생각 없어.
I am not going to discuss about this.
당연. 승부다!
Of course. We'll have a match!
-누가 저널리스트로서 위냐!
-인기투표로 정하자!
-Who's a better journalist?!
-We'll find that out by popularity vote!
-기한은!
-1주간 있으면 충분하지!
-And the duration?!
-One week is enough!
-다음 주 금요일!
-Next week Friday!
아리카?
Arika?
결전! 특종 전투
Showdown! Scoop Fight
(en: Scoop of the Century)
나, 꼭 아리카한테 투표할 거야!
I'll vote for you, Arika!
고마워. 되도록 힘내 볼게.
Thank you. I'll try my best.
그런 소릴 해서...
Well, you've said it.
그러게. 잘못 선택했어.
Yeah. It was a bad idea.
왜? 나, 아마자케 신문 좋아. 재밌고 흥미롭고! 아리카, 그대로 해 줘!
Why? I like your Amazake News. It's interesting and funny! Arika, keep it on like that!
그래?
I wonder.
그래! 나도 아리카처럼 말하고 싶은 걸 말하고 적고 할 수 있으면 좋겠다고...
Yeah! I want to write and talk what I want to speak out like you, Arika.
생각해.
But...
어?
Hm?
아, 그러니까, 힘내 줘!
Anyway, please do your best!
응! 맡겨 둬, 모로미!
Yeah! Leave it to me, Moromi!
좋아! 특종 찾아서 방송부를 찌부려 주겠어!
Alright! I'll find a great scoop and make that Broadcasting Club speechless!
내 탄환하고 박박군 아이스크림하고 뭐가 더 중요해?!
What's more important - my bullets or Hardhard Ice Creams?!
박박군 아이스크림인 게 당연하잖아, 멍청아!
It's obvious that it's Hardhard Ice Creams, you idiot!
뭐야, 이 새끼가? 박박 펀치다, 이 새꺄!
How dare you say that?! I'll give you a hardhard punch, you bastard!
왠지 대단한 걸 한 둘이라고는 안 보이네.
They don't look like they did something great.
어?
What?
준우승. 세계 선수권에서.
He got the second place in the world championship.
아!
Oh!
특종을 찾았어! 고마워!
I found a good story! Thanks!
역시 1천만 화소 최고급 디지털 카메라!
I knew this top class 10MP digital camera will worth it!
이 화질, 이 가벼움, 이것만 있으면 내 승부는...
What a quality it has! How light it is! My victory is sure with this...
아야야야...
Ouch...
왜 그래?
What's wrong?
그럼 준우승이 결정된 순간의 기분은?
So, how did you feel when the 2nd place was confirmed?
그건 뭐라고 할까, 참으로 복잡미묘한...
What should I say... truly complex and delicate...
멋진 척하지 마! 너 돌아가서 완전 신나 날뛴 주제에.
Don't try to act cool! When you went back, you were bouncing around damn happily!
너 그런 소리 할 거야?!
Do you really have to say that?!
그래서 세계 제 2인 둘은 사적인 공간에서도 호흡이 맞는 모습을 보였다...고.
And those two, who are the 2nd in the world, acted in good coordination even in their private space.
아리카, 잘 적어 주네!
Arika, you're really writing it well!
멋지게 잘 부탁해!
Make it as cool as possible!
당연하지! 음양 초등학교의 초 유명인!
Of course! You two are the super celebrities of Ginjou Elementary School,
텐료 잇키 and 메타비!
Tenryo Ikki and Metabee!
아마자케 신문에서만 둘의 독점 인터뷰를 읽을 수 있어!
People can read exclusive interview with you guys, only in Amazake News!
화제의 독점이 될 게 당연하지!
Of course it will become an exclusive yet well-known topic!
또 시끄러워지는 거야? 힘들어지겠네.
Will we be lionized again? That'll make us busy!
바보. 잇키보다 내가 큰일이지.
Fool! I'll be even busier than you, Ikki!
거짓말쟁이.
You liar.
네, 네, 아무래도 좋으니까. 그보다도.
Yeah, yeah, whatever. Just answer this:
혈액형에 좋아하는 음식에 싫어하는 과목 방침에 더, 큰 목소리로!
Your blood type, the food you like, the subject you hate, your policy of things, and answer in a loud voice!
어, 음, 그게...
Well, um, that's...
그런 일이 있었구나. 만약 지면 어쩔 거야?
So that was what happened. What are you going to do if you lose?
꼴사납고 모두의 웃음거리가 되어 버리겠지.
You'll be so unsightly and become a laughingstock of everyone.
안심해.
Don't worry.
내가 힘이 되어 줄게.
I'll help you.
이걸 네게 줄게.
I'll give it to you.
저...
Uh...
그래도...
But...
그거라면 분명 널 도와줄 거야.
That will help you.
무엇보다도 특별제니까 말이야.
Most of all, it's a special one.
뭐야.
What was that?
메, 메다로트?
A- a Medarot?
FLC형 플레임캐스트
FLC Type Flamecast
무엇을 노립니까.
What are you looking for?
노, 노리다니?
L- look for, what?
제가 찍을 수 없는 것은 없습니다.
I can take picture of anything.
승리의 비밀, 로보틀의 극의란?
What is the secret to the victory in Robattles?
암호는 신뢰 그리고 결단.
The password is trust and determination.
그 순간, 둘이 생각한 것, 지금 모든 것을 밝힌다!
What did they think at that very moment? We're about to find it out!
역시 준우승자! 옳은 소리 하네!
They really are runner-ups! They sure talk big!
어이, 읽었으면 비켜!
Hey, if you're done reading, then move!
사람 많네, 아리카!
What a crowd, Arika!
예상대로야.
Just as I thought.
야, 방송부 특별방송 봤어? 대단해!
Hey, did you look the special broadcast from Broadcasting Club?! It's awesome!
-뭐야, 그거?
-그게 말야, 정말 최고야!
-What's that about?
-You'll know when you see! It's the best!
-가 보자!
-어디에 있어?
-Let's go see that!
-Where is it!
뭐야, 어떻게 된 거야?
What's going on?
어, 잇키다!
Hey, it's Ikki!
정말이야!
True!
잇키! 잇키! 잇키! 잇키! 잇키! 잇키! 잇키! 잇키!
Ikki! Ikki! Ikki! Ikki! Ikki! Ikki! Ikki! Ikki!
-뭐, 뭐야?!
-W- what's this?!
에, 또다시. 4개째야. 대단해.
He's doing it again. It's already fourth. He's pretty good!
음? 왜 그러지?
Huh? What's wrong?
저런.
Too bad.
그러니까 적당히 먹어야지.
That's why he should know his limits.
죄송합니다, 죄송합니다, 죄송합니다, 죄송합니다! 어?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Huh?
메타비, 살려줘!
Metabee, help me!
빨리빨리빨리빨리빨리!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
저거 뭐야?!
What's that?!
시청각실
Audiovisual Room
오호, 잇키!
Hey, Ikki!
최고! 정말 잘 웃겨준다, 잇키!
You're the best! You make all of us laugh, Ikki!
어?
Huh?
유명인?
Am I famous already?
어라? 신문부가 이런 곳에서 뭐하고 있어? 취재 안 가도 돼?
Huh? What is a member of Newspaper Club doing here? Don't you have to go make a story?
지루하고 안 웃긴 기사 쓰기 위해 말야.
To write an uninteresting and not funny article, that is.
분해!
How vexing!
분해! 분해! 분해!
How vexing! How vexing! Damn vexing!
괜찮아. 아직 진 거 아니잖아.
It's alright. It's not like you have lost yet.
진정해.
Calm down.
알겠어!
I get it!
분하지만 역시 독자는 웃을거리하고 험담이나 찾나 봐.
It's vexing, but it seems that the readers only want gossips and things to laugh at.
남의 불행은 내 행복이렸다!
Whoever else's misfortune is my luck!
뭘 느릿느릿 걷고 있냐? 나에 씨한테 안 가?
Why are you walking so slowly? Aren't you going to see Ms. Nae?
부끄러워.
I'm embarrassed.
어?
What?
부끄럽다고! 나도 잇키 너하고 똑같은 놈으로 보이잖아!
I'm embarrassed of you, dammit! People are gonna think I'm on the same level with you, Ikki!
어?
Huh?
잘도 태연하네, 넌!
How can you be so calm?!
어? 인기있으니까 됐잖아! 이야, 인기인은 괴롭네! 뭘 해도 소문이 나니까!
Well, it's alright as I'm famous! Being famous is painful, you know! Whatever I do, people get to know about it!
그런 문제가 아냐.
You're not getting it, are you?
어, 이거...
Huh? Well...
그래그래! 시험보다 성적보다 인기인이 되는 게 중요해!
Yeah, yeah! Being famous is more important than tests and grades!
그러다 호되게 당한다.
You'll regret doing that.
이야, 괴롭네, 괴로워! 헤헤!
I'm so painful, damn painful! Heh!
괜찮을까...
I wonder if it's alright...
쉿! 들키겠다!
Shh! They'll find out!
괜찮아. 내가 더욱더 인기인으로 만들어 줄 테니까.
It's alright. I'll make him even more famous than now.
생각한 대로야.
Just as I thought.
괜찮을까...
Will it be okay?
어, 괜찮아, 괜찮아!
Yeah, of course, don't worry!
그래도 너무 한 게 아닐까...
But you might have overdone it...
방송부 인간이 왜 여기 있냐?
Why is someone from Broadcasting Club here?
베꼈겠다!
You've copied me!
어라? 대단한 트집이네.
That's some big claim you're making.
그럼 저거!
But, that!
그래, 특종이야! 내가 찾은 특종이다! 분하면 더 대단한 특종을 찾아 보여줘 봐.
Yeah, it's a scoop! It's a special story I found! Go find and show me even better scoop if you can find one!
다들다들다들다들! 시꺼! 니들 좀!
Hey, you guys! Everyone! Silence! Shut up, please!
특종! 저 세계 선수권 준우승자가 시험지를 버려?
A scoop! That famed world championship runner-up throws away his exam paper?!
유명인의 의외의 악취미 발견! 넌 용서받을 수 있을까!
That's one bad habit of a famous person! Will you be forgiven?!
아리카!
Arika!
임마, 내 비밀을!
Hey, that's my secret!
뭐야, 가면 갈수록 더 주목받는 인기인!
What is it, you center of attention?
그, 그래?
I- is that so?
아니! 아냐! 이거 때문에 난 선생님한테 불려가서 설교 듣고 게다가 숙제도 받았어! 봐봐, 이거!
No, it isn't! Because of this, I was called by teacher, got scolded, and got extra homework! Look at this!
잘 됐잖아?
Isn't it great?
어?
What?
인기인이 된 것 뿐만이 아니라 한자까지 외우다니!
Not only you became a famous person, but also you get to memorize Chinese characters!
내버려 줘.
Let it be!
이히, 그, 그래?
Heh, i- is that so?
아니, 아니야! 관계 없어!
No, it isn't! It has nothing to do with it!
뭔 소리야! 무엇보다도 주목받는 게 대단한 거잖아!
What are you saying?! Being in the center of attention is a great thing!
그, 그렇다고 내 비밀을 밝혀도 되는 거야?!
D- does that mean you can expose my secrets?!
돼! 신문은 읽혀져야 신문. 유명인은 이야기되어야 유명인.
It does! A newspaper is a newspaper when people read one. A famous person is famous when people talk about him!
그러지 못하면 그냥 종이조각! 일반인!
If people don't, it's just a scrap of paper! An ordinary person!
뭐, 뭔 소리야.
G- get real!
내가 잇키를 더더욱 인기인으로 만들어 주겠어!
I will make you even more famous, Ikki!
개, 개소리 마! 더는 하지 마!
D- don't fool around! Never do it again!
어, 잇키!
Hey, Ikki!
저런, 기삿거리가 도망쳤네.
Too bad. Your material has run away!
날 따라하니까 그렇게 된 거야. 분하면 더 대단한 특종을 찾으면 돼.
That happened because you copied me. If you're mortified, then go find an even better scoop!
물론이야. 당연하지.
Of course. Needless to say.
아리카...
Arika...
어차피 방송부가 이길 거야. 힘내 봐.
Broadcasting Club will win, eventually. Try your best, though.
금요일 인기 투표 기대되는걸.
I'm already looking forwards to the popularity vote in Friday.
아리카, 역시 이런 건 너무 나간 게...
Arika, you really are overdoing this.
그럼 아무것도 하지 마? 아무것도 하지 말고 져?
Then should I do nothing? Should I do nothing and lose?
난 싫어! 나는... 하고 싶은 걸 하고 적고 싶은 걸 적고 그럴 거야!
I won't! I... I want to write what I want to!
아리카!
Arika!
그래, 그래서 말야, 최후에 골 들어가서 저 버렸지 말야.
Yeah, we allowed a goal to them and that's how my team lost at end.
-정말?
-어, 엄청 분했어!
-Really?!
-Yeah, it was truly vexing!
-그래서 말야, 다음 시합은 꼭 이길 거야.
-응, 힘내!
-I'll win next time no matter what!
-Great, do so!
응.
Yeah.
하고 싶은 것.
What I wanted to do...
좋아, 좋은 느낌! 다음 아마자케 신문엔 길모퉁이 NG 특집이야!
Yeah, it looks great! Next Amazake News will feature NG scenes from street corners!
있잖아, 꼭 이겨야 해?
Hey, do you really have to win that badly?
뭔 소리야?
What are you talking about?
지금의 아마자케 신문, 별로야. 이전이 좋았어.
I don't like Amazake News of now. I liked the previous ones.
그럼... 그럼 신문부 없어져도 좋단 거야?
Then... then, are you saying that Newspaper Club can disappear?!
그런 소리 안 했어!
I didn't say that!
모로미도 브라스도 왜 응원 안 해 줘? 내가 져도 좋아?
Why aren't you and Moromi not supporting me? Are you fine with me losing?
그게 아니야. 그게 아니지만...
That's not it. That's not true, but...
재미있으면 뭐라도 된다는 건 좀...
saying whatever's fine as long as it's interesting doesn't feel right...
아니라고 생각해.
It's not right.
난 꼭 이기고 싶어. 브라스는 아니야?!
I want to win no matter what. Is that not true for you, Brass?!
-그건 이기고 싶지만...
-그렇지?!
-I do want to win, but...
-You know it!
특종의 예감!
I smell a good scoop over there!
아리카!
Arika!
방해하지 마! 내 기삿거리야!
Don't get in my way! That's my story!
개소리! 빠르면 됐지!
Don't fool around! Being quick is everything!
그래?
Oh, you think so?
플레임캐스트, 전송!
Transfer Flamecast!
아리카!
Arika!
브라스!
Brass!
뭐 해?!
What are you doing?!
셔터 찬스.
Shutter Chance.
브라스! 위!
Brass! Up!
비겁한 놈! 브라스, 일어나!
You coward! Stand up, Brass!
필름 와인더.
Film Winder.
되감기.
Rewind.
브라스!
Brass!
네, 치즈.
Yes, Cheese.
내 플레임캐스트는 특별제야!
My Flamecast is special!
신문부, 방송부에 지다!
Newspaper Club loses to Broadcasting Club!
그렇게 되겠지.
That's how it'll become.
-그, 그만해!
-줄게, 이런 거.
-S- stop it!
-You can take this.
어차피 뭔 특종도 안 되겠지만.
You won't get any scoop, though.
너희들답지 않게 졌네.
You guys lost, but that's not like you.
봐주기라도 했어?
Did you go easy on him?
그럴...지도. 싸우고 싶지 않았어. 이기면 취재에 가야만 하니까.
May...be. I didn't want to fight. I would have to go to gather news if I won.
마스터한테는 똑바로 말했어?
Did you tell your master?
믿을 수가 없어! 배틀이 제대로 시작되지도 않았는데 공격해 오다니!
I can't believe this! They came to attack when the battle hasn't even begun properly!
게다가 속임수를 써서 이기다니! 특별제라는 게 그거야? 특별히 비겁해?
Moreover, they cheated to win! Is that what being special is about? Specially cowardly?
아리카, 잠깐.
Arika, come with me.
어?
Huh?
이 상처 왜 몰랐니?
How did you not notice this wound?
메다로트 상태 알아채지도 못한 주제에 특별히 비겁하다느니 말할 처지가 못 되겠는데.
When you didn't even realize your Medarot's status, you aren't in position to call someone especially cowardly.
너 이기면 된다니 뭐 중요한 거 잊고 있는 거 없냐?
Aren't you forgetting something important, to say that winning is all?
알아!
I know what I have to know!
특종이냐?
A scoop?
말해 두는데, 난 한자 숙제가 싫어서 이런 소리 하는 게 아니니까.
Let me let you know that I'm not saying this to you because I don't want to do Chinese character homework.
아리카...
Arika...
아리카!
Arika!
모, 모로미?
M- Moromi?
오, 방과 후의 교실에 소녀 혼자 무엇을 생각하는가?
Look! What is this girl thinking about alone in the classroom after the school is over?
오, 이건 분명 러브레터! 우리 방송부는 저 편지를 손에 넣어 내용을 밝힙니다.
That must be a love letter! At Broadcasting Club, we will show what's written on that letter for you!
그럼 그 행운의 사내의 이름은?
So, what is the name of that fortunate man?
그만둬!
Stop it!
오, 방해 공작일까요?!
Could it be a sabotage?
이런 걸 해도 괜찮다 생각해? 사람 마음을 구경거리로 만들고?
Do you think it is right to do this? You're making a show out of one's heart!
뭔 소리야! 이건 알 권리, 알릴 의무란 거야!
What are you talking about? It's about the right to know and duty to tell!
본인이 알리고 싶지 않다는 걸? 웃기지 마!
It's something that one doesn't want to let it known in public! Don't fool around!
너야말로 비슷한 짓 했잖아! 지금와서 멋진 척 마!
You did the same thing already! Don't act as if you're cool, and different now!
멋진 척 하느라 말하는 게 아니야!
This is not about acting cool!
그럼 뭐야! 뭔 생각인데!
Then what is it about? What're you thinking?!
저널리스트야.
About being a journalist.
뭐, 뭔 큰 소리를 하는 거야.
Y- you're suddenly talking big?
플레임캐스트! 됐으니까 찍자! 상대 남자!
Flamecast! Let's film it! Find out who's the recipient male!
하지 마!
Don't!
브라스!
Brass!
힘으로 막겠단 거냐? 아깐 꽤나 봐줬는데 말야.
You're trying to stop me by force? I went easy on you before today.
같은 수는 다시는 안 통해.
That won't work agian.
-조준!
-네이!
-Aim!
-Yessir!
-찍는다!
-찍어!
-Film it!
-Start!
플레임캐스트!
Flamecast!
필름 와인더!
Film Winder!
우, 움직임이 완전히 달라.
T- the movement is completely different!
힘내!
Do your best!
젠장, 지면 안 돼! 처리해 버려!
Damn, don't lose! Take care of her!
하드 타깃.
Hard Target.
줌 인.
Zoom In.
필름 와인더.
Film Winder.
되감기.
Rewind.
코, 코쿠류한테 받은 메다로트였는데...
I- it was a Medarot that Kokuryu gave...
사랑 없는 메달 따위 허무한 거야.
A medal without love is in vain.
취재도 마찬가지. 상대에게 사랑과 존경을 가지지 않으면 단지 험담일 뿐!
It's same for making coverage. Without love and respect, it's nothing more than an insult!
잘못 생각하고 있었어. 괜히 너무했어.
I was wrong. I was uselessly bad.
잇키, 미안!
Ikki, I'm sorry!
너 찍고 있었어?
Were you filming me?!
모로미, 다시 아마자케 신문 읽어줄 거야?
Moromi, will you read Amazake News again?
응. 아리카, 고마워!
Yeah. Thank you, Arika!
신문부.
Newspaper Club.
이것도 신문부.
Newspaper Club again.
방송부                                     신문부
Broadcasting Club               Newspaper Club
신문부.
Newspaper Club.
네, 방송부.
Yeah, Broadcasting Club.
아마자케 신문: 공적!! 세계 제 2의 콤비 참새를 구하다!!
Amazake News: An achievement!! The 2nd pair in the world saves a sparrow!!
저런 쓸데없는 기사에 지다니 이 세상은 틀렸어.
The world is wrong, to vote for a boring news article like that!
진 건 진 거. 약속 지켜라.
You have lost, and that's it. Keep the promise.
그래서, 무리하게 함께할 필요 없는 것으로 이야기가 되어서...
And it seems that you two won't have to combine forcibly...
-그럼 신문부와 방송부는...
-이대로?
-Then Newspaper Club and Broadcasting Club
-are not changing?
그것도 신문에 쓰면 어때?
Make an article out of that, too!
너무해! 대체 다 뭐였던 거야?
They're bad! What was all that about, then?
그래도 두 가지 잘 됐잖아?
But at least two good things happened!
어?
Huh?
그렇구나! 그럼 다른 하나는?
I see! Then what's the other one?
(example: 候 and 侯)
젠장! 한자 획 한두개 다른 걸 어떻게 구분해?!
Damn it! How do I distinguish two characters with the only difference of one line?!
뭐, 한자 외우는 것도 득이라는 것!
Well, now you know! Being able to memorize more Chinese characters is the another!
제기랄!
Damn!
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
밤의 음양 초등학교에 울리는 기분 나쁜 목소리.
A eerie voice resounds in Ginjou Elementary School in night.
그것은 무서운 병원균에 감염된 메다로트의 절망의 외침인가?
Is that a cry of Medarots, infected by scary viruses?
아니면 사악한 밤의 왕, 돈 드라큐리오가 부르는 승리의 개선가인가.
Or is it a song of victory sung by Don Draculio, the evil king of night?
좀비화된 메다로트를 구하기 위해 악마가 숨어 있는 밤의 과학실에 결심하고 돌입한 잇키와 메타비.
To rescue the zombified Medarots, they break into the science room in night, where a devil awaits.
그 운명은 어찌?
What will happen to them?
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 괴담: 밤의 과학실
Next time on Medarot Damashii!
Ghost Story: Science Room in Night
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!